Anubha Bharti

Frontend Developer



- ✓ bhartianubha9@gmail.com
- 9380756358
- Banaglaore india
- indian
- **##** 05/02/1996
- Https://github.com/Anubha001/re act-tech-store,
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/anubhabharti-95535a145/

₽ PROFILE

Senior Frontend developer with 4.9+ years of experience in web developer, coding websites and applications. Well-versed in JavaScript, React.js, HTML, CSS; plus modern libraries and framework. Equipped with a record of success in consistently identifying and providing the technological needs of product through ingenious innovation.



english

hindi





PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

publicis sapient Associate L2

08/2021 - present | banaglore, india

The Container store custom closet:-

- Developed an interactive layout, using HTML5, SASS/SCSS/CSS, JavaScript (ES2015+), Typescript and React.js to generate an improved user experience and ensure compliance with web standards, accessibility, high-quality design and cross-browser compatibility.
- Worked collaboratively with Git and other team members including art directors, motion and 3D artists, web developers, creative technologists, project managers and strategists to continually expand application capabilities.
- Conducting code reviews, reviewing pull requests, troubleshooting, and optimising the performance of existing product features to continuously improve the user experience and security.
- Implemented, maintained and developed unit testing, end-toend (e2e) testing ,automated software testing processes to ensure/improve quality assurance.
- Collaborated with UX/UI designers, backend developers, and product managers to create/ensure seamless integration of REST APIs backend services with frontend functionalities, user experiences, implement creative ideas and visions for the frontend.
- Developed and maintained technical documentation for the frontend codebase, resulting in reduction in onboarding times for new developers.
- Worked with Agile development methodologies and continuously improved the team's work.
- Created reusable code libraries supporting Storybook, reducing development time for future projects and improving the efficiency of the development team.
- Used modern build tools and deployment processes, such as Webpack..

capgemini

Associate Consultant/B1

11/2020 - 08/2021 | bangalore, india

General Electric Corporate (Tech Stack: React Js) Project - GE Corp

- Worked on the speed optimization performance on GE
 Digital news website.Implemented a new responsive approach
 which increased the trafic optimised components for
 performance and scalability
- Build ge.com components from scratch and which is in production and currently customers are using it. Also worked on the GE Aviation interactive elements for the turboprop engine where user can directly interact with all the engine feature of Driving force fight

Nineleaps Technology Solutions Pvt Ltd software developer 1

07/2018 - 11/2020 | bangalore, india

Project - Virgin Voyages (Tech Stack: React Js, Redux (Thunk))

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT, **TYPESCRIPT**

REACT / REDUX / FRONT-END /

HTML, CSS, SCSS / CSS3 STYLED COMPONENTS, BOOTSTARP, MATERIAL **UI,ANT DESIGN**

GITHUB / JEST / REACT **TESTING LIBRARY**

JSON:API / RESTFUL APIS /RESPONSIVE DESIGN **STORYBOOK** SWAGGER/OPENAPI / NPM / RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN PRINCIPLES / SASS, LESS /

WEBPACK, END-TO-END (E2E) TESTING

- Worked on Voice Input Recognition, how a user can submit the answers by speech
- Vendor Module was made live. (Features were vendor list, filter, detail, add vendor form, pending list, approval list, dashboard, vendor activity slot, complain list, edit vendor, log complain, reject/review slot, settle vendor, adjust count and amount). Solely responsible for building products from scratch to deployment. I was also appreciated by the team lead for showing skills of smart work, team player and dedication towards achieving goals
- I have also coached my junior colleague while working over this project. Worked on Activity Module where anyone travelling on the ship can avail the entertainment package.
- Developed OTP generation using Node.Js
- Achieved 100% test coverage, no lint errors and 0% technical debt



EDUCATION

B.TECH

college of engineering and management kolaghat 09/2014 - 06/2018 | kolkata, india